Guide to the Rice Unversity Center for Research in Parallel Computation (CRPC) records, Ken Kennedy, Scientific Director, 1989-1999 UA 125
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Photographs and Slides, 1990-1998
  - 13 Negative Sheets and 9 Photos 1994 Caltech Minority Youth Program (Box 15, Item 7)
  - 6 Photos K-12 Activities in Computer Science, July 31, 1993 (Box 15, Item 8)
  - 14 Photos Spend A Summer with a Scientist, 1993 (Box 15, Item 9)
  - 3 Photos SAS Students and Blackside Magazine, 1994 (Box 15, Item 10)
  - 14 Photos and 7 Negatives South Texas Academy Program Summer, 1993 (Box 15, Item 11)
  - 12 Photos and 8 Negative Sheets South Texas Academy Internship Summer, 1994 (Box 15, Item 12)
  - 14 Negatives and 1 Photo Outreach, undated (Box 15, Item 13)
  - 2 Negatives Sheets 1994 Caltech Minority Program (Box 15, Item 14)
  - 20 Photos Rice Location Shots, undated (Box 15, Item 15)
  - 5 Negatives Rice Staff, undated (Box 15, Item 16)
  - 6 Negatives CRPC Brochure, undated (Box 15, Item 17)
  - 20 Slides CRPC Location Shots, undated (Box 15, Item 18)
  - 18 Slides CRPC Location Shots, undated (Box 15, Item 19)
  - 27 Slides CRPC Location Shots, undated (Box 15, Item 20)
  - 20 Slides People with Computers, undated (Box 15, Item 21)
  - 31 Photos Conference Rooms Rayzor/Sewell Hall, undated (Box 15, Item 22)
  - 39 Photos Conference Rooms Labs, undated (Box 15, Item 23)
  - 15 Photos Conference Rooms Shepard/Hammon/Kelley, undated (Box 15, Item 24)
  - 41 Negatives Conference Rooms, undated (Box 15, Item 25)
  - 1 Photo Duncan Hall Architect's Drawing, undated (Box 15, Item 26)
  - Caricatures and Cartoons by Colorado Bill Crowley, of CRPC staff and faculty, 1995 (Box 15, Item 27)
- Series III: Technical Reports and paper materials, 1989-1999
  - Technical Reports Index Last Updated August 1, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - CRPC-TR89042: Sizing and Least Change Secant Methods, J. E. Dennis, H. Wolkowicz, November 1989 (Box 16, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90043: Parallel Program Debugging with On-the-fly Anomaly Detection, R. Hood, K. Kennedy, J. Mellor-Crummey, March 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90044-S: Incremental Dependence Analysis, Carl M. Rosene, Ph.D. thesis, March 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR89045: Experiments with Multicomputer LU-Decomposition, E. F. Van de Velde, Concurrency, Practice, and Experience Vol.2, No. 1, April 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90046: What is Easy? Eric F. Van de Velde, March 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90049 Alternative Orderings, Multicoloring Schemes, and Consistently Ordered Matrices, David L. Harrar II, June 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90050-S: Intermediate Languages for Debuggers, Benjamin Chase, May 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90051: Automatic Blocking of Nested Loops, Robert Schreiber, Jack Dongarra, May 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90052-S: The ParaScope Editor: User Interface Goals, Kathi Fletcher, Ken Kennedy, Kathryn McKinley, Scott Warren, May 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90054: Algorithms for Scalable Synchronization on Shared-Memory Multiprocessors, John Mellor-Crummey, Michael L. Scott, April 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90055: On the Orthogonality of Eigenvectors Computed by Divide-and-Conquer Techniques, Dan Sorensen, P. Tang. Appears in SIAM Journal of Numerical Analysis, 28, no. 6, (December 1991), pp. 1752-1775, May 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90056: A Primer for Program Composition Notation, K. Mani Chandy, Stephen Taylor, June 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90057: An Implementation of a Divide and Conquer Algorithm for the Unitary Eigenproblem, G. S. Ammar, L. Reichel, Dan Sorensen, June 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90058: Interprocedural Optimization: Eliminating Unnecessary Recompilation, Michael Burke, Keith D. Cooper, Ken Kennedy, Linda Torczon, July 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90059: An Experiment with Inline Substitution, Keith D. Cooper, Mary Hall, Linda Torczon, (Appeared in Software-Practice and Experience, 21(6) June 1991), July 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90060: Experiences in Writing a Distributed Particle Simulation Code in C++, David W. Forslund, Charles Wingate, Peter Ford, J. Stephen Junkins, Jeffrey Jackson, Stephen C. Pope, July 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90061-S: Improving Parallelism after Inline Substitution, Mary Hall, July 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90062: The Onset of Thermal Runaway in Partially Insulated or Cooled Reactors, M. J. Ward, E. F. Van de Velde, July 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90063-S: Experience with Interprocedural Analysis of Array Side Effects, Paul Havlak, Ken Kennedy. Appeared in IEEE Transactions on Parallel and Distributed Systems 2(3), July 1991, August 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90064: Loop Distribution with Arbitrary Control Flow, Ken Kennedy, Kathryn S. McKinley, August 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90065: Unexpected Side Effects of Inline Substitution: A Case Study, Keith D. Cooper, Mary Hall, Linda Torczon (Appeared in ACM Letters on Programming and Systems, 1(1), March 1992), September 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90066: Direct Search Methods on Parallel Machines, J. E. Dennis, V. Torczon. Appeared in SIAM Journal on Optimization, Vol. 1, pp. 448-447, 1991, September 1990 (revised March 1991) (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90067: Mesh Independence for Nonlinear Least Squares Problems with Norm Constraints, M. Heinkenschloss. Appeared in SIAM Journal on Optimization Vol. 3 (1992) 81-117, August 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90068-S: Analysis of Synchronization in a Parallel Programming Environment, Jaspal S. Subhlok, Ph. D. thesis, August 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90069: A Domain Decomposition Method for Parabolic Equations Based on Finite Elements, Clint N. Dawson, Qiang Du, Todd F. Dupont, October 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90070: A Finite Difference Domain Decomposition Algorithm for Numerical Solution of the Heat Equation, Clint N. Dawson, Qiang Du, Todd F. Dupont, October 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90071: A Finite Element Domain Decomposition Method for Parabolic Equations, Clint N. Dawson, Qiang Du, October 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90072: Modeling of 'in situ' Biorestoration of Organic Compounds in Groundwater, Chen Y. Chiang, Clint N. Dawson, Mary F. Wheeler, October 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90073: ADOL-C, A Package for the Automatic Differentiation of Algorithms Written in C/C++, A. Griewank, D. Juedes, J. Srinivasan, December 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90074: Implementing Automatic Differentiation Efficiently, D. Juedes, A. Griewank, October 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90075: Increasing the Granularity of Parallelism and Reducing Contention in Automatic Differentiation, Brad N. Karp, Christian H. Bischof, November 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90076: Criticality in Reactors under Domain or External Temperature Perturbations, Eric Van de Velde, Michael J. Ward, October 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90077-S: Parallel Domain Decomposition Method for Mixed Finite Elements for Elliptic Partial Differential Equations, Lawrence C. Cowsar, Mary F. wheeler, November 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90078: Investigation of the 2d 0(3) Model Using Overrelaxation Algorithm, John Apostolakis, Clive F. Baillie, Geoffrey C. Fox, Syracuse University, December 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90079: FORTRAN D Language Specification, D. C. Fox, S. Hiranandani, K. Kennedy, C. Koelbel, U. Kremer, C. Tseng, M. Wu, December 1990 (revised April 1991) (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90081: Numerical Studies of Electron Dynamics in Oblique Quasi-Perpendicular Collisionless Shock Waves, P. C. Liewer, V. K. Decyk, J. M. Dawson, B. Lembege, December 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90082: Spectral Element Solutions for the Navier-Stokes Equations on High-Performance Distributed Memory Parallel Processors, Paul F. Fischer, December 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90083: Achievements and Prospects for Parallel Computing, Geoffrey Fox. Presented at the International Conference on Parallel Computing: Achievements, Problems, and Prospects, Italy, June 3-9, 1990, June 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90084: The Finite Element Solution of Elliptical Systems on a Data Parallel Computer, Scott Hutchinson, Edward Hensel, Steven Castillo, Kim Dalton, August 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90085: The Finite Element Solution of Two-Dimensional Transverse Magnetic Scattering Problems on the Connection Machine, Scott Hutchinson, Steven Castillo, Edward Hensel, Kim Dalton, April 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90086: LAPACK Working Note 25: LAPACK Block Factorization Algorithms on the Intel iPSC/860, Jack Dongarra, Susan Ostrouchov, October 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90087: LAPACK Working Note 28: The IBM RISC System/6000 and Linear Algebra Operations, Jack Dongarra, Peter Mayes, Giuseppe Radicati di Brozolo, December 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90088: LAPACK Working Note 26: Prospectus for an Extension to LAPACK: A Portable Linear Algebra Library for High-Performance Computers, E. Anderson, C. Bischof, J. Demmel, J. Dongarra, J. DuCroz, S. Hammarling, W. Kahan, November 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR91089: Compile-Time Generation of Communications for Scientific Programs, Charles Koelbel, January 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90090: Physical Computation, Geoffrey Fox. Presented at the International Conference on Parallel Computing: Achievements, Problems, and Prospects, June 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90091-S: Computational Results with Another Method of Solving Very Long and Thin LPs, Petra Mutzel, May 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90092: An Error Analysis for Galerkin Approximations to an Equation of Mixed Elliptic-Parabolic Type, Todd Arbogast, October 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90093: A Static Performance Estimator to Guide Data Partitioning Decisions, Vasanth Balasundaram, Geoffrey Fox, Ken Kennedy, Uli Kremer, October 1990 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90095: Explicit/Implicit, Conservative, Galerkin Domain Decomposition Procedures for Parabolic Problems, C. N. Dawson, T. F. Dupont, October 1990 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90096: Interactive Parallel Programming Using the ParaScope Editor, Ken Kennedy, Kathryn McKinley, Cahu-Wen Tseng. Appeared in IEEE Transactions on Parallel and Distributed Systems (2)3, July 1991t, October 1990 (revised March 1991) (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90097: Implicit Application of Polynomial Filters in a k-Step Arnoldi Method, D. C. Sorensen, October 1990 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90098: A Robust Trust Region Algorithm for Nonlinear Programming, Karen Williamson, April 1990 (revised May 1991) (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90100-S: Microlocal Regularity of an Inverse Problem for the Multidimensional Wave Equation, G. Bao, November 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90101-S: Aggressive Live Range Splitting, Preston Briggs, Keith D. Cooper, Linda Torczon, November 1990 (revised March 1991) (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90102-S: Goal-Directed Interprocedural Optimization, Preston Briggs, Keith D. Cooper, Mary W. Hall, Linda Torczon, November 1990 (updated June 1992) (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90103-S: Practical Dependence Testing, Gina Goff, Ken Kennedy, Chau-Wen Tseng, November 1990 (revised March 1991) (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90104: Non-interactive Estimation of the Marmousi Velocity Model by Differential Semblance Optimization: Initial Trials, W. W. Symes, August 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90105: Compiler Support for Unstructured Scientific Computations, Charles Koelbel, Piyush Mehrorta, December 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90106: Analysis and Transformation in the ParaScope Editor, Ken Kennedy, Kathryn McKinley, Chau-Wen Tseng, December 1990 (revised April 1991) (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90107: The Reflection Inverse Problem for Acoustic Waves, W. W. Symes, December 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR90108: The Power Test for Data Dependence, Michael Wolfe, Chau-Wen Tseng, December 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90110: On the Superlinear and Quadratic Convergence of Primaldual Interior Point Linear Programming Algorithms, Y. Zhang, R. A. Tapia, J. E. Dennis. Appeared in the SIAM Journal on Optimization, Vol. 2, pp. 304-324, 1992, January 1990 (revised April 1991) (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR90111: On the Superlinear Convergence of Interior Point Algorithms for a General Class of Problems, Y. Zhang, R. A. Tapia, F. Porta, March 1990 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR91112: Semicoarsening Multigrid on a Hypercube, Richard A. Smith, Alan Weiser, January 1991 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90113: Gauge Theories on the Random-Block Lattice, T. W. Chiu, North-Holland Physics Publishing, August 1990 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR91114-S: Deterministic Annealing, Clustering, and Optimization, Kenneth Rose, Ph.D. thesis, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR90115-S: Parallel Hierarchical N-Body Methods, John K. Salmon, Ph.D. thesis, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR91116: Preconditioned Projection Methods for Sparse Unsymmetric Eigenproblems, Gautam M. Shroff, January 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR91117: Gravitational Forces in Dual Porosity Models of Single Phase Flow, Todd Arbogast, March 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR90119: A Quadratically Convergent Polynomial Primal-Dual Interior-Point Linear Programming Algorithms, R. A. Tapia, Yin Zhang, June 1990 (revised April 1991) (Box 17, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR91120: Parallel Problem Architectures and Their Implications for Portable Parallel Software Systems, White paper and articles from Rhode Island DARPA Workshop, Geoffrey Fox, February 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR91121: An Overview of the Fontran D Programming System, Seema Hiranandani, Ken Kennedy, Charles Koelbel, Ulrich Kremer, Chau-Wen Tseng, March 1991 (revised August 1991) (Box 17, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR91122: A Semi-Coarsening Multigrid Algorithm for SIMD Machines, J. E. Dendy, Jr., M. P. Ida, J. M. Rutledge, April 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR91171: On the Convergence of the Iteration Sequence in Primal-Dual Interior-Point Methods, Y. Zhang, R. A. Tapia, Y. Ye, July 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR91171: The Architecture of the Problems and Portable Parallel Software Systems, Geoffrey Fox, August 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR91173: Experiences Using the ParaScope Editor, M. Hall, T. Harvey, K. Kennedy, N. McIntosh, K.S. McKinley, J.D. Oldham, M. Paleczny, G. Roth, September 1991 (revised April 1992) (Box 18, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR91174: Parallel Programming with PCN, I. Foster, S. Tuecke, ANL-91/32, September 1991 (revised January 1993) (Box 18, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR91175: A Quadratically Convergent O(√nL)-Iteration Algorithm for Linear Programming, Y. Ye, O. Guler, R.A. Tapia, Y. Zhang, August 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR91176-S: Coloring Register Pairs, Preston Briggs, Keith D. Cooper, Linda Torczon, October 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90177: Multioffset Inversion by Differential Semblance Optimization, W. Symes, December 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR91178-S: An Upper Bound for the Linearized Map of an Inverse Problem for the Wave Equation, G. Bao, W. Symes, February 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR91179: Segmented Data Files: an I/O Standard, William Symes, May 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR91181: Successive Element Correction Algorithms for Sparse Unconstrained Optimization, Guangye Li, September 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR91182: A Column-Secant Update Technique for Solving Systems of Nonlinear Equations, Guangye Li, Tingzhan Liu, September 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR90183: The Predictor Corrector Interior-Point Method as a Composite Newton Method, R. Tapia, Yin Zhang, M. Saltzman, A. Weiser, July 1990 (revised August 1991) (Box 18, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR91185: ADIFOR – Generating Derivative Codes from Fortran Programs, ANL/MCS-P063-0991, Christian Bischof, Alan Carle, George Corliss, Andreas Griewank, P. Hovland. Appears in Scientific Programming, no. 1 (1992), pp. 1-29, December 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR91186: Hierarchical Tree-Structures as Adaptive Meshes, David J. Edelsohn, November 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR91187: Thermal Simulation of Pipeline Flow, Philip T. Keenan, September 1991 (revised August 1993) (Box 18, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR91188: MIPLIB: A Test Set of Real-World Mixed Integer Programming Problems, Robert E. Bixby, E. Andrew Boyd, Ronni R. Indovina, November 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR91189: DO and FORALL: Temporal and Spatial Control Structure, Min-You Wu, Wei Shu, Syracuse University, SCCS-139, November 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92190: Optimizing for Parallelism and Data Locality, Ken Kennedy, Kathryn S. McKinley, January 1992 (revised and renamed May 1992) (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92191: A Diagonal-Secant Update Technique for Sparse Unconstrained Optimization, Guangye Li, January 1992 (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR91192: Lessons from Massively Parallel Applications on Message Passing Computers, Geoffrey Fox, December 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR911193: Empirical Relations Between Static and Dynamic Exponents for Using Model Cluster Algorithms, P.D. Coddington, C.F. Baillie. Appears in Physical Review Letters, vol. 68, no. 7, September 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92194: An Implementation of a Parallel Primal-Dual Interior Point Method for Block Structured Linear Programs, Irvin J. Lustig, Guangye Li. Report was known as "An Implementation of a Parallel Primal-Dual Interior Point Method for Multicommodity Flow Problems.", January 1992. Revised and renamed in June 1992 (Box 18, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR91195: Interprocedural Compilation of Fontran D for MIMD Distributed Memory Machines, M. W. Hall, S. Hiranandani, K. Kennedy, C. Tseng. Appearing in Proceedings of Supercomputing '92, November 1991 (revised September 1992) (Box 18, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR91196: Evaluation of Compiler Optimizations for Fortran D on MIMD Distributed Memory Machines, S. Hiranandani, K. Kennedy, C. Tseng, November 1991 (revised April 1992) (Box 18, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92197-S: Automatic Software Cache Coherence through Vectorization, Ervan Darnell, John M. Mellor-Crummey, Ken Kennedy, January 1991 (revised April 1992) (Box 18, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92198: The Use of Physics Concepts in Computation, Geoffrey C. Fox. Submitted for Publication as Chapter 3 of the book, "Computation: The Micro and the Macro View", February 1992 (Box 18, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR91199: Implementation of an Interior Point LP Algorithm on a Shared-Memory Vector Multiprocessor, Matthew J. Saltzman, November 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92200: Procedure Cloning, Keith D. Cooper, Mary W. Hall, Ken Kennedy. Appeared in the IEEE International Conference on Computer Languages, April 1992, February 1992 (Box 18, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92201: An Empirical Exploration of the Poincare Model for Hyperbolic Geometry, Joe Austin, Joel Castellanos, Ervan Darnell, Marcia Etrada, March 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92202: Evaluating Parallel Languages for Molecular Dynamics, Terry W. Clark, Reinhard von Hanxleden, Ken Kennedy, Charles Koelbel, L. Ridgway Scott. Appeared in the IEEE Computer Society Press in the Proceedings of the Scalable High Performance Computing Conference held in Williamsburg, Virginia, April 26-29, 1992, February 1992 (Box 18, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92204: Static Performance Estimation in a Parallelizing Compiler, Ken Kennedy, Nathaniel McIntosh, Kathryn McKinley. Report was known as "Static Performance Estimation", April 1992. Revised and renamed in May 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR91205: Automatic Data Alignment and Distribution for Loosely Synchronous Problems in an Interactive Programming Environment, Ken Kennedy, Eli Kremer, April 1991 (revised March 1992) (Box 18, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92206: PDS: Direct Search Methods for Unconstrained Optimization on Either Sequential or Parallel Machines, Virginia Torczon, March 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92207-S: Relaxing SIMD Control Flow Constraints Using Loop Transformations, Reinhard von Hanxleden, Ken Kennedy, April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92208-S: Compiler Blockability of Numerical Algorithms, Steve Carr, Ken Kennedy, April 1992 (revised January 1993) (Box 18, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92209: Implementation of Electromagnetic Scattering from Conductors Containing Loaded Slots on the Connection Machine CM-2, Yinghua Lu, A. Gaber Mohamed, R. F. Harrington. Joint Paper between NPAC and the Department of Electrical Engineering, Syracuse University, March 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92210: High Performance Scalable Matrix Algebra Algorithms for Distributed Memory Architectures, Geoffrey C. fox, A. Gaber Mohamed, Gregor von Laszewski, Manish Parashar Neng-Tan Lin, Nagkang Yeh, April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92211: A Hierarchical Availability Model for Multiprocessor Computers. A. Gaber Mohamed, Salim Hariri, Hasan B. Mutlu, March 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92212: Blocked LU Factorization on a Multiprocessor Computer, A. Gaber Mohamed, Geoffrey C. Fox, Gregor von Laszewski, March 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92213: 1992 CRPC Applications Report, Geoffrey Fox, April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92214-S: Automatic and Interactive Parallelization, Kathryn S. McKinley, April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92216: Generation of Standard Bilinear Programming Test Problems, Paul Calamai, Luis Vicente, Joaquim Judice, April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92217: A Compiler Approach to Scalable Concurrent Program Design, Ian Foster, Stephen Taylor, April 1992 (revised July 1992) (Box 18, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92218-S: Register Allocation via Graph Coloring, Preston Briggs, April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 9, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92219: Parallel Computing in Industry – An Initial Survey, Geoffrey, May 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92220: Variations of Structured Broyden Families for Nonlinear Least Squares Problems, Hiroshi Yabe, June 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92221: Fast, Contention-Free Combining Tree Barriers, Michael L. Scott, John M. Mellor-Crummey, June 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92222-S: Memory-Hierarchy Management, Steve Carr, September 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92223: Efficient Call Graph Analysis, Mary Hall, Ken Kennedy, July 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92225: High Performance Fortran Language Specification, Version 1.0, High Performance Fontran Forum, October 1992 (Box 19, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92229-S: Physical Optimization Algorithms for Mapping Data to Distributed-Memory Multiprocessors, Nashat Mansour, Ph.D. thesis, NPAC, Syracuse University SCCS-345, August 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3, Item 1)